blogster.com 2010-06-14

# Blogster - Blogster

## PRIVACY NOTICE

BLOGSTER.COM collects, retains, and uses information about customers and other visitors to the site only for specific business purposes, including to protect and administer customer records and accounts; to comply with certain laws and regulations; to help design or improve BLOGSTER.COM items and services, and to understand customers' needs so that we can provide them with high-quality items and service.

If BLOGSTER.COM believes it has a legitimate business reason for sharing identification and other personal information with a third party, such as to offer the customer certain discounts, products or services, it may share such information with third parties. BLOGSTER.COM may also disclose information about its customers to third parties as required or permitted by applicable law.

## INFORMATION GATHERED

The information BLOGSTER.COM learns from customers helps to personalize and continually improve the customer's experience at BLOGSTER.COM. BLOGSTER.COM may gather the following types of information (if provided by a user):

  * Surname and forename
  * Preferred language
  * Delivery address and billing address
  * E-mail address
  * Website addresses/URL's
  * Telephone numbers
  * Facsimile numbers
  * Social security or other national ID numbers
  * Items purchased
  * Bank card information including card type, number, expiry date, security code, card holder's surname and forename, and billing address.

BLOGSTER.COM uses the information that the customer provides for purposes such as responding to the customer's requests, customizing future shopping for him or her, and communicating with him or her.

In addition, BLOGSTER.COM may also use standard software to collect non-identifying information about customers and other visitors to the site, such as: 

  * Date and time the site was accessed; 
  * IP address (a numeric address given to servers connected to the Internet); and 
  *   * Web browser used (collectively, "Anonymous Information"). 

BLOGSTER.COM hopes that by using Anonymous Information, it can update the site to make it more useful to you and other visitors. BLOGSTER.COM reserves the right to maintain, update, disclose or otherwise use Anonymous Information, without limitation.

## NOMENCLATURE DATA

In accordance with the Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act of April 13 2000, nomenclature information concerning customers may be processed automatically.

This processing is required in order to process customer orders. By indicating his or her e-mail address, the customer may receive confirmation of his or her order but also information on BLOGSTER.COM promotions as well as on events via the Internet.

BLOGSTER.COM reserves the right to collect information concerning customers, including by use of cookies when a customer's web browser accesses BLOGSTER.COM and, if it desires, reserves the right to transmit the information so collected to business partners and others as described below.

The customer may object to disclosure of his or her personal information by so informing BLOGSTER.COM by submitting the modification of personal information request form on the website.

In the same way, the customer has a right of access, modification and rectification of personal data about himself or herself, in accordance with the Canadian Federal Law of 13 April 1978 and other laws. This right may be exercised via e-mail or by submitting the modification of personal information request form on the website.

## SECURITY

BLOGSTER.COM protects the security of a customer's information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information the customer inputs.

It is important for a customer to protect against unauthorized access to his or her account, password, and to his or her computer.

## SHARING OF INFORMATION

Gathering information about customers is an important part of BLOGSTER.COM business, but it is not in the business of selling that information to others. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, BLOGSTER.COM shares customer information only as described herein.

Business Transfers: As BLOGSTER.COM continues to develop its business, it might sell or buy companies, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that BLOGSTER.COM or all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

Protection of BLOGSTER.COM and Others: BLOGSTER.COM releases account and other personal information when it believes release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our policies and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of BLOGSTER.COM, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction; however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing or otherwise disclosing personal information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.

With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, a customer will receive notice when information about him or her might go to third parties, and the customer will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

BLOGSTER.COM reserves the right to resolve system problems using means including, but not limited to, examining accounting logs and other records, accessing an account's mailbox and any other means necessary to ensure proper functioning of the system. BLOGSTER.COM does not guarantee the security of any data on the system including data transmitted using secure servers. BLOGSTER.COM assumes no liability for the loss of private or confidential material. BLOGSTER.COM customers should be aware that no computer system/network is completely safe from system failures or intrusions by unauthorized parties, and therefore no sensitive material should be passed through the network.

## RETENTION

BLOGSTER.COM retain personal information for as long as we have a business need for it or as applicable laws or regulations or government orders require us to retain it. We maintain an information retention policy that is designed to comply with applicable laws and regulations. Customer information is stored in BLOGSTER.COM computer system. That information is used to respond to any inquiries by the customer, to provide customer service, to customize future shopping for customers, to respond to any governmental or other inquiries regarding sales or other taxes, and for no other purpose.

## PRIVACY OF CHILDREN

BLOGSTER.COM encourages parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their children's online activities. BLOGSTER.COM strictly adheres to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information from any child under the age of 13 in any manner that violates this law.

## LINKS

BLOGSTER.COM may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. deliveries to California addresses is not responsible for the collection or use of your personal information or Anonymous Information at any third party sites. Therefore, BLOGSTER.COM disclaims any liability for any third party's use of your personal information or Anonymous Information obtained through using the third party web site.

## DISPUTE RESOLUTION

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by Indiana law, without giving effect to any choice or conflict of law provision or rule.

For deliveries to California addresses, pursuant to California law, BLOGSTER.COM and the customer agree that any and all disputes, claims or controversies arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy shall be submitted to an arbitrator chosen and paid by BLOGSTER.COM. Prior to the arbitration, a period of time shall be allowed for the discovery or exchange of non-privileged information relevant to the dispute. The dispute shall be determined by arbitration in the customer's hometown area, before one arbitrator. Judgment on the Award may be entered in any court having jurisdiction. This clause shall not preclude parties from seeking provisional remedies in aid of arbitration from a court of appropriate jurisdiction.

For all other disputes between BLOGSTER.COM, it[s] owners and/or employees and you as user of the site, and/or services offered within, and/or provided within this site arising out of use of this site or services offered within this site regardless of the manner of resolution, shall be arbitrated, litigated (tried in a court of law), or otherwise resolved by a tribunal located in Marion County, Indiana.

## MODIFICATION OF PRIVACY POLICY

BLOGSTER.COM reserves the exclusive right, at its discretion, to update, change, modify, add, or remove portions of BLOGSTER.COM and this Privacy Policy. The effective date of the latest version of the Privacy Policy, as stated below, indicates the last time the policy was materially modified. Checking the effective date below allows the customer to determine whether there have been material modifications since the last time he or she reviewed the policy.

The Privacy Policy was last materially modified on November 12, 2008.

The customer's continued use of BLOGSTER.COM following any change in the Privacy Policy will constitute his or her acknowledgement and acceptance of such change. If he or she does not agree to any change, he or she must immediately stop using and accessing BLOGSTER.COM.

## CUSTOMER RELATIONS

For any information, queries or complaints regarding the policy, the customer may contact BLOGSTER.COM by submitting the modification of personal information request form on the website.
